(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-14T01:56:36.162828",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
私が私のことを愛して
I love myself,
何が悪いのかしら？
what's wrong with that?
痛いだとか変わってるだとか
They say I'm cringey or weird,
届きませんね　そのリプライ
but your replies don't reach me.
大好きなお洋服　大好きなやお化粧で
With my favorite clothes and favorite makeup,
お決まりのハーフツイン巻いておでかけしよう
and my iconic half-twintails curled, I'll go out!
日傘持って　ぼっちだって幸せだもん！
Holding a parasol, I'm happy even being alone!
Chu！　可愛くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being so cute,
生まれてきちゃってごめん
sorry that I was born.
Chu！　あざとくてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being calculatingly cute,
気になっちゃうよね？ごめん
sorry that you can't ignore me.
Chu！　可愛くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being so cute,
努力しちゃっててごめん
sorry for working hard on myself.
Chu！　尊くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being precious,
女子力高くてごめん
sorry for being a girly girl.
ムカついしちゃうよね？ざまあw
It annoys you, right? You deserve it!
あなたはあなたのことだけどどうぞ
Worry about your own business,
私に干渉しないでください
please don't meddle in mine.
類は友を呼ぶと言うけど
They say birds of a feather flock together,
届きませんね　その陰口
but your gossip doesn't reach me!
私が私の事愛して 何が悪いのでしょうか?
Loving myself, what's wrong with that?
嫉妬嫉妬して?
Are you jealous?
届きませんね。そのリプライ
I won't hear your replies.
大好きな洋服 大好きなお化粧でお出かけしよう
Let's go out dressed in my favorites!
日傘持って ぼっちだって 幸せだもん!
Happy all on my own!
Chu! 可愛くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being cute.
生まれてきちゃってごめん
Sorry for being born.
Chu! あざとくてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being crafty.
気になっちゃうよね?ごめん
Does it catch your eye? Sorry!
Chu! 可愛くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being cute.
努力しちゃっててごめん
Sorry for working hard on myself.
Chu! 尊くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being precious.
女子力高くてごめん
Sorry for having high girl power.
ムカついちゃうよね?ざまぁw
Does it piss you off? Too bad, lol.
負けたくない 恐くもない あんたらごとき
I won't give in to anyone!
一番大切にしてあげたい
I want to make my own choices most dear to me.
それが 私
That's who I am.
Chu! 可愛くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being cute.
生まれてきちゃってごめん
Sorry for being born.
Chu! あざとくてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being crafty.
人生楽しんでごめん
Enjoying life!
Chu! 可愛くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being cute.
目立っててごめん
Sorry for standing out.
意識しちゃうよね?ごめん
Does it catch your attention? Sorry!
Chu! 可愛くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being cute.
努力しちゃっててごめん
Sorry for working hard on myself.
ムカついちゃうよね?ざまぁw
Does it piss you off? Too bad, lol.
(間奏)
(Instrumental break)
(Music transition)
トウキョウ・シャディ・ランデヴ
Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous
あなたにも忘れたいことない? ないことあるのかしらね
Is there anything you want to forget?
知らない映画なのに涙を流すのは
Even though I don't know the movie, I shed tears.
くだらないことを考えてばかりね
Thinking only about pointless things...
雨が上がれば愛もその横顔も誰かのものになるのでしょう
When the rain stops, someone else will take you.
嘘っぱちのファンデーションも全部 今夜のためよ
All this fake foundation is for tonight.
なのに一体全体何をして何故?
Why on earth is it never enough?
トウキョウ・シャディ・ランデヴ
Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous!
曖昧な本当なんてメランコリカ化するだけ
Vague truths just turn into melancholy.
あたしをさあ引っ掴んで今テイクオンミー
Take me away right now!
(間奏)
(Instrumental interlude)
年中リップサービス鈍感かましては撃日
Year-round lip service, insensitive bashing...
どんがらかっしゃんフィールガールは涙の目にも二万ヤ
Feel girls are devils even with teary eyes!
頭の中のミュージックのせいであなたの話は一向に聞き取れない
Because of the music in my head, I can't hear you at all.
冗談じゃないわ トウキョウ・シャディ・ランデヴ
No way, Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous!
その時が来ったってどうにもなんないぜ
Even when that time comes, nothing will change.
曖昧な本当なんてメランコリカ化するだけ
Vague truths just turn into melancholy.
ホロライブカウントダウン 2023~2024
Hololive Countdown Live 2023-2024!
盛り上がっていくよ!
Let's get even more hyped!
電波テンポアップして絶賛感電中!
The radio wave tempo has increased and the excitement is electrifying!
あなたにも忘れたいことないこと あるのかしら
I wonder if there are things you want to forget, things that make you sad, too
知らない映画なのに涙を流すのはドラマが足りないからでしょ
I shed tears at movies I don't know because they lack drama
そんな愚にも付かないくだらないこと考えてばかりね
I'm always thinking about such stupid things and pointless things
雨が上がれば愛もその横顔も誰かのものになるのでしょう
When the rain stops, love and that profile will belong to someone else
嘘っパチのファンデーションも全部 今夜のためよ
All the fake foundations are for tonight, but why on earth?
トウキョウ・シャディ・ランデヴ
Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous
その時が来ったって何にもならないぜ
Even if the time has come, there's nothing I can do
曖昧な本当なんてメランコリ化するだけ
Vague truths only make you melancholic
あたしをさあ引っ掴んで今テイクオンミー
Come on, snatch me away, take me on now
ちゅ、多様性。
[Song: Chu, Tayousei.]
我 愛你 酔い が 覚め ない
Wo ai ni, I'm so intoxicated
oh, i need you 恋 が 醒め ない
Oh I need your love, I'm not clear-headed
お生憎様の慣れ果て察して
Oh baby, I can’t imagine what this mess will be
無問題 破滅してみて
Moumantai, go on you’re ruining it
hold me tight トラウマの味
Hold me tight, the taste of trauma makes it
猛反対 お手お座りでハイ報酬
More like mine, so sit and let me make it worth your time
喉の奥がチクンチクン
I feel a tingle in the back of my throat
僕はドクンドクン
My heart’s pounding, listen close
心臓ごと引きずり出してみてよ
Reach on in and pull it out so you would see me bare it all
気持ちいいね面倒くさいけど やっぱ照れくさいけど
I'm feeling good, but it’s quite a troubling thing...
死ぬまで忘れられないチューしよ
...kiss me till we're super dead
ゲゲゲロゲゲゲロゲロチュー
Get get get on! Get get get on! Get on chu!
隅から隅に送られた気持ちが
Emotions overflowing, spilling out escaping my mouth
堪えられないでしょ
It’s melting hot, isn’t it mesmerizing?
ゲゲゲロゲゲゲロゲロチュー
Get get get on! Get get get on! Get on chu!
ボンジカ 勝負はいつもボンジカ
Pon chi kan, you should know it’s a game I...
僕に言わせりゃ珍部が ボインで最後はロマンでしょ
...Ton chin kan, have always dominated
もうなんか やられればいいもうやんない 忘れられない
One night of pleasure, can't forget it
終わんないでドキメキ偏愛予習
All my life I want this crush to chain me by your side
喉の奥がチクンチクン
I feel a tingle in the back of my throat
僕はドクンドクン
My heart’s pounding, listen close
心臓ごと引きずり出してみてよ
Reach on in and pull it out so you would see me bare it all
気持ちいいね面倒くさいけど やっぱ照れくさいけど
I'm feeling good, but it’s quite a troubling thing...
死ぬまで忘れられないチューしよ
...kiss me till we're super dead
イカれた街はゾンビで溢れる
Now in this crazy city, zombies are overflowing
君は僕に恋してる
I can see the start of you falling for me
ときめく胸に繋がるロープを引けよ
I hear it beating faster, so I’ll gather all of the rope
ゲゲゲロゲゲゲロゲロチュー
Bet bet bet on! Bet bet bet on! Bet on chu!
花の塔
[Song: Hana no Tou]
君が持ってきた漫画 くれた知らない名前のお花
Remember when we talked about manga,
今日はまだ来ないかな 初めての感情を知ってしまった
suddenly flowers had blossomed inside my heart.
窓に飾った絵画をなぞって ひとりで宇宙を旅して
Tracing on the window, even though I’m alone
それだけでいいはずだったのに
and space travel will take me to the unknown.
君の手を握ってしまったら 孤独を知らないこの街には もう二度と帰ってくることはできないのだろう
If I hold your hand my dreams will become complete...
もう二度と帰ってくることは
...we don’t have to go back; my future is in your eyes.
君が持ってきちゃったのね
You brought it with you, didn't you?
くれた知らない名前のお花
A flower with an unknown name you gave me.
今日はまだ来ないかな?
Won't you come today either?
初めての感情知ってしまった
I've come to know emotions for the very first time.
窓に飾った絵画をなぞって
Tracing the painting decorated on the window,
ひとりで宇宙を旅して
traveling through the universe all alone,
それだけでいいはずだったのに
even though that should have been enough...
孤独を知らないこの街には もう二度と戻ってくることはできないのだろう
To this town that knows no loneliness, I could never return again.
君が手を差し伸べた 光で影が生まれる
Where you reached out your hand, light creates a shadow.
歌って聞かせて この話の続き 連れて行って 見たことない星まで
Sing and let me hear the rest of this story, take me to a star I've never seen.
誰の手も声も届かない 高くそびえ立った塔の上
Atop the tower towering high, where no hands or voices reach,
飛ばすフウセンカズラ
balloon vine seeds are sent flying.
僕は君に笑って欲しいんだ
I want you to smile.
満たされない穴は 惰性の会話で
The unfulfilled voids were brushed aside with idle talk,
誤魔化して これまでは埋めてきたけど
filling them up until now, but...
退屈な日々を散乱させて
Scattering boring days,
君と二人でこの街中を泳いできたら
if we swam through this town together,
素敵なことでしょう?
wouldn't that be wonderful?
出したことないほど 大きな声で
With a voice louder than ever before,
やっと君に伝わる 歪なくらいが
it finally reaches you. A distortion just about right
きっとちょうどいいね 世界の端と端を結んで
must be just right, connecting the ends of the world.
窓に飾った絵画をなぞって ひとりで宇宙を旅して
Tracing the painting decorated on the window, traveling through the universe alone,
それだけでも不自由ないけれど 僕は選んでみたいの
even though that's freedom enough, I want to choose...
高鳴る心悸だらけの空を 安全なループを今 描き換えて!
the sky full of throbbing palpitations, redrawing the safe loop now!
君の手を握ってしまったら 孤独を知らないこの街にはもう二度と戻ってくることはできないのだろう
If I were to hold your hand, I could never return to this town that knows no loneliness.
いくらでも迷いながら 光も影も見に行こう
Hesitating however much, let's go see both light and shadow.
歌って聞かせて この話の続き 連れて行って 見たことない星まで
Sing and let me hear the rest of this story, take me to a star I've never seen.
君の手を握ってしまっては
If I were to hold your hand,
孤独を知らないこの街には
to this town that knows no loneliness
もう二度と帰ってくることはできないの
I could never return again...
祈って
Praying...
いくらでも迷いながら
Hesitating however much,
光も影も見に行こう
let's go see both light and shadow.
歌って聞かせて
Sing and let me hear...
この話の続き
the rest of this story,
連れて行って 見たことない星まで
take me to a star I've never seen.
世界の端と端を結んで
Connecting the ends of the world,
connecting the ends of the world,
結んで
connecting...
もうすぐ時計は6時
Soon the clock will strike six.
もうそこに一番星
The first star is already there.
影を踏んで 夜に紛れたくなる帰り道
Stepping on shadows, on the way back home wanting to blend into the night.
どんなに探してみてても
No matter how much I search,
一つしかない星
there is only one star.
何億光年 離れたところからあんなに輝く
Shining so brightly from hundreds of millions of light-years away.
離れたところから あんなに輝く
From so far away, shining so brightly...
いいな 君は みんなから愛されて
Must be nice, you're loved by everyone.
「いいや 僕は ずっと一人きりさ」
"Not at all, I've always been all alone."
君と集まって 星座になれたら
If you and I could gather and become a constellation,
星降る夜 一瞬の願い事
a falling star's night, a momentary wish.
きらめいて ゆらめいて 揺れているシグナル
Glittering, flickering, a shaking signal.
君と集まって 星座になれたら
If you and I could gather and become a constellation,
空見上げて 指を差せるような つないだ線 解かないで
looking up at the sky and pointing our fingers, don't untie the connecting lines.
君がどんなに 眩しくても
no matter how dazzling you might be.
ハルカカナタ ボクラワ デアッテシマッタ
Far away, we happened to meet.
カルマだから 何度も出会ってしまおう
Because it's karma, we'll meet over and over again.
雲の隙間で
In the gaps between the clouds...
もうすぐ時計は8時 夜空に満天の星
Soon it will be 8 o'clock, the night sky full of stars.
何のこれしき 離れたところには もうないかもしれない
In places far away, they might not even exist anymore.
月が綺麗で 泣きそうになるのは
The moon is so beautiful, making me feel like crying
いつの日にか 別れが来るから
because a parting will come someday.
君と集まって 星座になれたら
If you and I could gather and become a constellation,
流れ星みたい 流れるひとりごと
like a shooting star, a flowing soliloquy.
君と集まって 星座になれたら
If you and I could gather and become a constellation,
切なる願い 誰かに届いたら
if a heartfelt wish reaches someone.
はるかかなた 僕らは出逢ってしまった
Far away, we happened to meet.
カルマだから 何度も出逢ってしまおう
Because it's karma, we'll meet over and over again.
雲の隙間で
In the gaps between the clouds...
君と集まって星座になれたら 夜空広げて 手が届きそうな
If you and I could gather and become a constellation, spreading the night sky where we can almost touch it,
暗闇を照らすような
illuminating the darkness...
だから集まって 星座になりたい
That's why I want to gather and become a constellation,
いろどりどりの光 放つような
emitting multicolored light.
つないだ線 解かないよ 君がどんなに 眩しくても
I won't untie the connecting lines, no matter how dazzling you might be.
群れを逸れて 夢をくわえた
Breaking away from the group, holding a dream,
それが最後になるような気がしたんだ
it felt like that would be the last time.
獣は素手を 一握り蒔いた
The beast scattered a handful of sand,
それが最後になるような気がしたんだ
it felt like that would be the last time.
不確かな夢 叶えるのさ 約束の夜にわおわお
Making an uncertain dream come true on the night of our promise, wow-wow!
微かな風に願うのさ 静寂の朝にわおわお
Wishing on a faint breeze in the silent morning, wow-wow!
遠い星の少年は その腕に約束の飾り
The boy from a distant star wears the ornament of promise on his arm,
まだ旅路の途中さ 幻惑の園に
still in the middle of his journey in the garden of illusion.
群れを逸れて夢を盗んだ
Straying from the pack, I stole a dream.
それが最後になる気がしたんだ
I felt like it would be my final moment.
獣は砂を一手盛り撒いた
The beast scattered a handful of sand.
それが最後になる気がしたんだ
I felt like it would be my final moment.
不確かな夢叶えるのさ 約束の夜に
Fulfilling an uncertain dream on a promised night.
微かな風に願うのさ 静寂の朝に
Wishing upon a faint breeze in the silent morning.
それが最後になる気がしたんだ
I felt like it would be my final moment.
手負いの夢を紡ぎ直せば
If I re-spin this wounded dream—
熱砂を蹴り抗うのだ 約束の前に
Kicking up the hot sand, I resist before the promise.
命綱はないのだ サーカスの夜に
There is no lifeline in the circus night.
まだ旅路の途中さ
I'm still midway on this journey,
あの場所に加速するさらに
accelerating even further toward that place.
雨上がりのシャンデリア 幻の園に
To the post-rain chandelier in the phantom garden.
迷走 smash
Aimless smash,
dribble trapper
kidding me now?
迷走 smash
Aimless smash,
dribble trapper
kidding me now?
coyote steals the sound
coyote steals the pass
coyote steals the sound and pass
swish da 着火 you
Swish da, ignite you.
pass code a " penetrator "
Passcode a "penetrator".
ベース！ bebop！
Bass! Bebop!
ゲット triple！ buzz up ビート！
Get triple! Buzz up beat!
ワンラブ and mercy！
One love and mercy!
bebop！ heat check！
Bebop! Heat check!
vasco da gama ビート！
Vasco da Gama beat!
pass code a " penetrator "
Passcode a "penetrator".
ベース！ bebop！
Bass! Bebop!
wanna buzz up ビート！
Wanna buzz up beat!
just wanna buzz up ビート！
Just wanna buzz up beat!
脳内 耕地 に extra pass
An extra pass in the mental fields,
クー アザ ドン イハビ
cool as a don i-ha-bi.
脳内 耕地 に extra pass
An extra pass in the mental fields,
クー アザ ドン イハビ
cool as a don i-ha-bi.
大丈夫さ
It'll be alright.
通り過ぎる Sound
Sounds passing by,
通り過ぎる Pass
passes passing by,
通り過ぎる Sound and Pass
sounds and passes passing by.
swish da 着火 you
Swish da, ignite you.
pass code a " penetrator "
Passcode a "penetrator".
ベース！ bebop！
Bass! Bebop!
ゲット triple！ buzz up ビート！
Get triple! Buzz up beat!
ワンラブ and mercy！
One love and mercy!
bebop！ heat check！
Bebop! Heat check!
vasco da gama ビート！
Vasco da Gama beat!
pass code a " penetrator "
Passcode a "penetrator".
ベース！ bebop！
Bass! Bebop!
wanna buzz up ビート！
Wanna buzz up beat!
just wanna buzz up ビート！
Just wanna buzz up beat!
脳内 耕地 に extra pass
An extra pass in the mental fields,
クー アザ ドン イハビ
cool as a don i-ha-bi.
swish da 着火 you
Swish da, ignite you.
努力 未来 A BEAUTIFUL STAR
Effort, future, a beautiful star.
ランドリー今日はガラ空きでラッキーデイ
Laundry is wide open today, what a lucky day.
かったりい油汚れもこれでバイバイ
Say goodbye to stubborn grease stains.
誰だ誰だ頭の中呼びかける声は
Who is that calling out inside my head,
あれが欲しいこれが欲しいと歌っている
singing about wanting this and wanting that?
幸せになりたい 楽しいて生きていたい
I want to be happy, I want to enjoy living,
この手に掴みたい あなたのその胸の中
I want to grasp in my hands, deep inside your chest.
ハッピーで埋め尽くして レストインピースまで行こうぜ
Fill it all up with happiness, let's go till we rest in peace.
愛をばらまいて アイラブユー罵ってくれ 全部奪って笑ってくれマイハニー
Scatter love, despise me, I love you; take everything and laugh, my honey.
努力 未来 A BEAUTIFUL STAR
Effort, future, a beautiful star.
なんか忘れちまってるんだ
It feels like I've forgotten something.
努力 未来 A BEAUTIFUL STAR
Effort, future, a beautiful star.
Effort, future, a beautiful star
努力 未来 A BEAUTIFUL STAR
ランドリー今日はガラ空きでラッキーデイ
Laundry today is empty and a lucky day,
かったりい油汚れもこれでバイバイ
say goodbye to stubborn oil stains.
誰だ誰だ頭の中呼びかける声は
Who is that, who is that voice calling out in my head?
あれが欲しいこれが欲しいと歌っている
Singing, "I want that, I want this."
幸せになりたい 楽しして生きていたい
I want to be happy, I want to live enjoying life.
この手に掴みたい あなたのその胸の中
I want to hold it in my hands, inside your chest...
ハッピーで埋め尽くしてレスタイピースまで行こうぜ
let's fill it up with happiness, let's go to rest in peace!
いつか見た地獄もいいところ愛をばらまいて
The hell I once saw is a good place too, scattering love around.
アイラブユー赦してくれ全部奪って笑ってくれマイハニー
I love you, forgive me, take everything and smile, my honey!
努力 未来 A BEAUTIFUL STAR
Effort, future, a beautiful star
4443で外れる炭酸水
Carbonated water spilling over at 4443...
ハングリー拗らせて吐きそうな人生
A hungry, twisted life making me want to puke.
「止まらない雨はない」より先にその傘をくれよ
Give me that umbrella before saying "there is no rain that won't stop."
あれが欲しいこれが欲しい全て欲しいただ虚しい
I want that, I want this, I want everything, I'm just empty.
幸せになりたい 楽しして生きていたい 全部滅茶苦茶にしたい
I want to be happy, live enjoying life, mess everything up,
何もかも消し去りたい
and erase everything.
あなたのその胸の中 ラッキーで埋め尽くしてレスタイピースまで行こうぜ
Inside your chest, let's fill it up with lucky things and go to rest in peace!
良い子だけ迎える天国じゃどうも生きらんない
She can't live in a heaven where only good children are welcome.
アイラブユー赦して奪って笑ってくれマイハニー
I love you, forgive me, take me away, laugh at me, my honey!
ハッピーラッキーこんにちはベイビー
Happy lucky, hello baby!
良い子でいたい そりゃつまらない
I want to be a good girl, that's boring.
ハッピーラッキーこんにちはベイビーソースイート
Happy lucky, hello baby, so sweet!
努力 未来 A BEAUTIFUL STAR
Effort, future, a beautiful star
努力 未来 A BEAUTIFUL STAR なんかすごい良い感じ
Effort, future, a beautiful star, I feel so good!
努力 未来 A BEAUTIFUL STAR
Effort, future, a beautiful star
本当は分かってた いけないことだって分かってたのに
To be honest, I knew. I knew it was wrong, but even so...
この手をすり抜ける全部が愛に見えたの
everything that slips through these hands looked like love.
確かめていた言葉が形になって揺れるだけ
The words I made sure of just take shape and waver.
引いて 描いて きっと それだけ
Strumming, drawing, surely just that.
つまらないな 正解の読み合わせ
Isn't it boring, reading and comparing answers?
あとちょっとで分かってたのに
Even though I was just a little close to figuring it out.
飲んで 吐いて 全部忘れちゃえ
Drinking, vomiting, forgetting everything!
水を目立たせた本心と鏡合わせ 見つめ合えたら
Looking at true feelings clad in water in opposing mirrors, once our eyes meet...
オーバー dosis 君とふたり やるせない日々
Overdose, you and me, the days that make me feel helpless.
解像度の悪い夢を見たい
I wanna dream of a blurred-out nightmare.
オーバー dosis 君とふたり 甘いハッタリ
Overdose, you and me, a sweet bluff.
don't stop it music, darling
本当に分かってる？いけないことだって分かってる？
Do you really know? Do you really know that it's wrong?
多分 時間だけが過ぎていく文言で満ちていく
Maybe only time is passing, filled with questions and answers.
言い訳する間もなく裸になってしまうだけ きっと溜まっていくんだずっと
I've got no time to make excuses, I'll just go naked; surely it'll keep piling up forever.
終わってしまえばいいとふっと思い描いて腐っていく あの甘い果実のように僕ら壊れていく
It'd be nice if we could end this abruptly, spoiling and rotting just like that sweet fruit, we start to break.
だから踊って 眠って 全部忘れちゃえ
That's why I dance, sleep, and forget everything!
嘘をかぶったあなたと隣り合わせ 見つめ合えたら
Next to you, all dressed in lies, once our eyes meet...
オーバー dosis 君とふたり 分かりたいのに
Overdose, you and me, even though I want to understand...
変に間抜けな嘘が嫌い オーバー dosis 君とふたり
I hate those strangely in-between lies. Overdose, you and me...
分かりたいのに
even though I want to understand.
two step from hell with me, darling
オーバー dosis 君とふたり やるせない日々
Overdose, you and me, the days that make me feel helpless.
解像度の悪い夢を見たい
I wanna dream of a blurred-out nightmare.
オーバー dosis 君とふたり 甘いハッタリ
Overdose, you and me, a sweet bluff.
don't stop it music, darling
本当は分かっていた
To be honest, I knew
いけないことだったって
I knew it was wrong,
分かっていたのに
even though I knew.
この手をすり抜ける全部が
Everything that slips through these hands
愛に見えたの
looked like love.
確めていた言葉が形になって 揺れるだけ
The words I made sure of take shape, only wavering.
引いて 描いて きっと その場凌ぎ
Strumming, drawing, only doing those for sure.
つまらないな 世界の読み合わせ
Isn't it boring, reading and comparing answers
あとちょっとで分かりかけていたのに
Even though I was so close to figuring it out.
飲んで 吐いて 全部忘れちゃって
Drinking, vomiting, forgetting everything,
水を押さえた本音と鏡合わせ
My true feelings clad in water, facing mirrors.
見つめ 合えたら
Once our eyes meet,
overdose 君とふたり
overdose, you and me,
やるせない日々よ
the days that make me feel helpless.
解像度の悪い夢を見たい
I wanna dream of a blurred-out nightmare.
overdose 君とふたり
Overdose, you and me,
甘いハッタリ
a sweet bluff.
don't stop it music, darling
胸ぐらを掴まれて強烈なパンチを
I was grabbed by the collar, got an intense punch,
食らってよろけて肩を並べてしゃがんだ
staggered, and crouched shoulder to shoulder with you.
予報通りの雨にお前におべんかい
The expected rain falls on you and me,
傷口が綺麗になるなんて嘘をつく
telling a lie that our wounds become clean.
いつも口喧嘩さえ
You can't even argue well
うまく出来ないくせにして
most of the time,
許せない冗談言うなよ
so don't say such unforgivable jokes.
あまりのつまらなさに目が潤んだ
It bored me to the point I teared up.
何度も青あざだらけで涙を流して流して
Being black and blue all over, shedding tears again and again,
不安定な心を肩に預け合いながら
resting our unstable hearts on each other's shoulders,
腐りきったバッドエンドに抗う
we fight against the depraved bad ending.
なぜだろう喜びよりも心地よい痛みズキズキと響いて
Somehow, this comfortable pain throbs deeper than joy,
濡れた服に舌打ちしながら腫れ上がった顔見合って笑う
clicking our tongues at wet clothes and laughing at our swollen faces.
土砂降りの夜に誓ったリベンジ
On this drenching night, we swore our revenge.
胸ぐらを掴み返して反撃のパンチを繰り出すくらいじゃなきゃお前の方の隣には立てないから
If I didn't grab you by the collar and punch you as my counterattack, I couldn't stand next to you.
相手がなんであれ日和らない何度されても諦めない
I'm not afraid of opponents no matter who they are, I don't give up even if I get knocked over.
忘れるな忘れるなと言い聞かせ続けた想い
I've kept reminding myself not to forget this feeling...
ああ傘はいらないか言葉を一つくれよ
Ah, will you give me a word instead of an umbrella?
ぬるい優しさではなく弱音に侵された
Not a lukewarm kindness, but words to gouge
胸の奥を抉るような言葉を
the deep inside invaded by weakness.
何度も青あざだらけで涙を流して流して
Being black and blue all over, shedding tears again and again,
不安定な心を肩に預け合いながら
resting our unstable hearts on each other's shoulders,
腐りきったバッドエンドに抗う
we fight against the depraved bad ending.
なぜだろう喜びよりも心地よい痛みズキズキと響いて
Somehow, this comfortable pain throbs deeper than joy,
濡れた服に舌打ちしながら腫れ上がった顔見合って笑う
clicking our tongues at wet clothes and laughing at our swollen faces.
土砂降りの夜に囚われの日々に
Like asking on this drenching night and on the trapped days,
問いかけるように光った瞳の中で
within the eyes shining as if questioning,
誓ったリベンジ
we swore this revenge.
子供はまるで雪の継承 君にプレゼントしたくても
Children are like the succession of snow, even if I want to present it to you,
無中になればなるほどに 形は崩れ落ちて溶けていって 消えてしまうけど
the more absorbed I get, the more its shape crumbles, melts, and disappears...
でも僕が選ぶ言葉が そこに託された想いが
But the words I choose, the feelings entrusted there,
君の胸を震わすのを 諦められない
I cannot give up on making them shake your heart.
愛してるよりも愛が届くまで
Until love reaches you more than "I love you,"
もう少しだけ待ってて
please wait just a little longer.
薄着でただ側に立ってても 不必要に汗を変えてしまう僕なんかは
Even if I stand right by your side in light clothes, sweating needlessly, someone like me...
どうしたって生ぬるくて 君を痛めつけてしまうのだろう
no matter what I do, is too lukewarm and might end up hurting you.
手のひらが熱いほど 心を冷たいんでしょ
The hotter my palms feel, the colder my heart must be,
冗談でもそんな残酷なこと言わないでよ
don't say such cruel things even as a joke.
別に見えないけど 前世をかけても ちゃんとくっかえさせてよ
I can't see it, but even if it costs me a past life, let me turn it around properly.
救いたい 救われたい このイコールが今
I want to save, I want to be saved, this equation right now
優しく剥がしていくんだよ
is gently peeling away.
くだらない論争 プライドの過剰包装
Useless argument, excessive packaging of pride,
正しさよりも優しさがほしい
I want kindness more than correctness.
そしてそれを 受け取れるのは 夢で一緒になりたいな 不特定でなくってただひとり 君であってほしい
And being able to receive that, I want us to be together in a dream, not with anyone unspecified, but just you alone.
掲げた言葉で 傷と日々を直そう
Let's fix our wounds and days with the words we raised.
そっとひとつ 確かすぎた熱量で
Softly, one by one, with a warmth that was too certain,
光ってしまっていたカーテン
a curtain that had been shining...
そんな失敗作は 重ねて 重ねて 重ねて
Such flawed creations are piled up, piled up, piled up.
見つけといていつか 最高のイチゴに行くを
Find it someday, let's take the ultimate step!
言葉はまるで雪の継承 君にプレゼントしたとして
Words are like the succession of snow, even if I present them to you,
時間が経ってしまえば溶いて 消えてしまっても
even if time passes, they melt and disappear...
だから僕らがストーリーに添えられた字幕のように 思い返した時 ふいに目をやる時に
So like subtitles added to our story, when we look back and catch our eyes unexpectedly,
君の胸を震わすもの探し続けたい 愛してるよりも愛が届くまで
I want to keep searching for something that makes your heart tremble, until love reaches you more than "I love you,"
もう少しだけ待ってて
please wait just a little longer.
もう少しだけ もう少しだけ
Just a little more, just a little more
踏み出せたのなら
if I could take a step forward
そう小さな優しさを 分け合えたのなら
yes, if we could share such a small kindness
ありふれた一日が 素敵な日になっていく
the ordinary day would become a wonderful day
ほらそうやって何度も 喜びはめぐる
see, no matter how many times joy comes around
慌ただしく過ぎる朝に いつも通り過ぎる朝に
In the busy morning, in the usual morning
頼まれたお使いと 予定を照らす君が教えてくれた
illuminating errands and plans you taught me
わかってる 欲しいんでしょう?
You know what I want, don't you?
艶やかなこの唇
These glossy lips
柔な男たち引き寄せる 息をのむほど甘い蜜
Drawing in frail men, sweet honey that takes your breath away
わかってる 欲しいんでしょう?
You know what I want, don't you?
二度見するこの身体
This body that makes people look twice
艶めく街 ひとり歩けば
Walking alone through the flushed city
淫らな視線がからみつく
Lewd gazes entangle around me
ねぇ 何を期待してるンなのは?
Hey, what are you expecting?
そのうちじゃなくて 今すぐがいいの
Not someday, I want it right now
大人の恋に焦がれて
Yearning for adult love
見た目よりも残る あどけない
Leaving behind appearance, only an innocent
心だけが先走る
heart races ahead
青い蕾のまま オトナブルー
Remaining as a blue bud, adult blue
わかってる 欲しいんでしょう?
You know what I want, don't you?
刺激する私のすべて
Everything about me that stimulates
冷めた瞳まで魅了する
Fascinating even cold eyes
いつかは花になる アマリリス ha!
Someday it will become a flower, Amaryllis, ha!
優しいだけの言葉じゃなくて
Not just kind words
心でつながりたくて
I want to connect by heart
ありきたりなメイクじゃ隠せない
Cannot be hidden with ordinary makeup
憧れだけ 夢を見る
Dreaming only of yearning
あなたの前で また オトナブルー
In front of you, adult blue again
優しいだけの言葉じゃなくて
Not just kind words
心でつながりたくて
I want to connect by heart
ありきたりなメイクじゃ隠せない
Cannot be hidden with ordinary makeup
憧れだけ 夢を見る
Dreaming only of yearning
まだ見ぬ恋路を 追いかけて 追いかけて
Chasing the unseen path of love, chasing and chasing
また オトナブルー
Adult blue again
優しいだけの言葉じゃなくて
Not just kind words
心でつながりたくて
I want to connect by heart
外出した瞬間 終わったわ
The moment I stepped outside, it was over
天気は良いのに進めない
The weather is nice, but I can't move forward
風強すぎて お亡くなり
The wind is too strong, I'm done for
定期 定期的にオールバック
Regularly, regularly getting an all-back
地下に潜りたいって思いました
I thought I wanted to hide underground
風さえなくなれば あったかいのに
If only the wind would stop, it would be warm
ずっと座りたいって思いました
I thought I wanted to sit forever
髪の毛 強風オールバック
Hair in a strong wind all-back
外出た瞬間終わった
The moment I stepped outside, it was over
天気はいいのに進めない
The weather is nice, but I can't move forward
風強すぎてお亡くなり
The wind is too strong, I might disappear
定期定期的にオールバック
Regularly, I put my hair all back
地下に潜りたいなって思いました
I thought I wanted to dive underground
風さえなくなればあったかいのに
If only the wind would stop, it would be warm
ずっと座りたいなって思いました
I thought I wanted to sit forever
いやいやと外でたら
But if I go outside, no, no, no
ハトハトハトハト大乱闘
It's chaos, chaos, chaos, chaos
外出た瞬間終わった
The moment I stepped outside, it was over
天気はいいのに進めない
The weather is nice, but I can't move forward
風強すぎてお亡くなり
The wind is too strong, I might disappear
定期定期的にオールバック
Regularly, I put my hair all back
風強すぎてお亡くなり
The wind is too strong, I might disappear
定期定期的にオールバック
Regularly, I put my hair all back
今年もみんなありがとう！
Thank you all for this year too!
来年のホロライブも勢いは止まらないぜ！
Hololive's momentum won't stop next year either!
外出た瞬間終わった
The moment I stepped outside, it was over
天気はいいのに進めない
The weather is nice, but I can't move forward
風強すぎてお亡くなり
The wind is too strong, I might disappear
定期定期的にオールバック
Regularly, I put my hair all back
地下に潜りたいなって思いました
I thought I wanted to dive underground
定期定期的にオールバック
Regularly, I put my hair all back
そう
That's right
外出た瞬間終わった
The moment I stepped outside, it was over
天気はいいのに進めない
The weather is nice, but I can't move forward
風強すぎてお亡くなり
The wind is too strong, I might disappear
地下に潜りたいなって思いました
I thought I wanted to dive underground
定期定期的にオールバック 髪の毛恐怖オールバック
Regularly, I put my hair all back, the fear of hair, all back
無敵の笑顔で荒らすメディア
Couldn't beat her smile, it stirred up all the media
知りたいその秘密ミステリアス
Secret side, I wanna know it so mysterious
抜けてるとこさえ彼女のエリア
Even that elusive side, part of her controlled area
完璧で嘘つきな君は
Complete and perfect, all you say is a bunch of lies
天才的なアイドル様
Dear miss genius idol, unmatched
今日何食べた? 好きな本は? 遊びに行くならどこに行くの?
What did you eat today? What book do you love? Whenever you go out for fun, tell me, where do you go?
何も食べてない それは内緒 何を聞かれてものらりくらり
Haven't eaten anything, it's a secret, unknown, always acting so vaguely
そう淡々と だけど燦々と 見えそうで見えない秘密は蜜の味
So unconcerned, although you brightly glow, any seemingly unveiled secrets are as sweet as honey
あれもないないない これもないないない
Essential lie, lie, lie
好きなタイプは? 相手は? さあ答え
So what is your type of guy? Any partner? So now, answer this...
誰かを好きになることなんて 私分からなくてさ
I don't have any idea how I could love anyone, cannot find out if it's true...
嘘か本当か知り得ない そんな言葉にまた一人堕ちる
...or it's a lie, once again, there's somebody who's fallen for the words and cues
誰もが目を奪われていく 君は完璧で究極のアイドル
That emotion melts all hearts, all eyes on you, 'cause you are perfect, the most ultimate idol
金輪際現れない 一番星の生まれ変わり
Unrivaled, will not appear again, it's the brightest star reborn, yes, indeed
その笑顔で愛してるで 誰も彼も虜にしていく
Using that smiling face, that "I love you" again, now, everybody is lured and captivated by you
その瞳がその言葉が 嘘でもそれは完全なアイ
The pupil that you got, the words you vocalize, even when untrue, it's your perfected ai
はいはいあの子は特別です 我々はハナからおまけです
Right, right, we all know she's very special, yes, we had lost the fight before it started, so impressed
お星様の引き立て役です 全部がその子のお陰なわけない
We're serving as support to her grace, cannot tell me everything was 'cause of her, no, it's not right, out of line
嫉妬嫉妬なんてないわけがない これはおふざけじゃないから許せない
How can we not feel jealous while being around, it's not a joke, you know, right? So I cannot forgive you for that
完璧じゃない君じゃ許せない 自分を許せない
Completely deny, imperfect you that i sight, myself, no pardon allowed
誰よりも強い君以外は認めない
I won't allow anyone if it's not you, strongest of all
誰もが信じ崇めてる まさに最強で無敵のアイドル
That emotion seized all hearts, worshipping you, yes, indeed, so strong, it's you, unrivaled idol
弱点なんて見当たらない 一番星を宿している 弱いところなんて見せちゃダメダメ
There cannot be weaknesses to find, the brightest star is residing in you, the gaps and shortcomings don't show 'em, dammit, dammit
知られたくないところは見せずに 唯一無二じゃなくちゃイヤイヤ
Parts nobody wants to know should remain hidden, one and only, if it's different, no way, no way
それこそ本物のアイ
Such a true love, it's the realest ai
得意の笑顔で沸かすメディア 隠しきるこの秘密だけは
Showing this smile, my own weapon boiling media, keeping everything about my secret deep inside
愛してるって嘘で積むキャリア これこそ私なりの愛だ
"I'm in love with you", my career is built on such a lie, it's the way i know to show my love, without a doubt
流れる汗も綺麗なアクア ルビーを隠したこの瞼
Running down, my sweat is flowing, cleanest aqua, right? Ruby hidden under my eyelids, where it resides
歌い踊り舞う私はマリア そう嘘は飛び切りの愛だ
I sing, and dance around, look at me, i'm maria, so lying surely is the greatest kind of love
誰かに愛されたことも 誰かのこと愛したこともない
I recall no one that loved me whole before, and i've not been in love with anybody before
そんな私の嘘が いつか本当にになること 信じてる
Now the lies i'm making up, i'm hoping that a day comes when they all become true, I keep believing
いつかきっと全部手に入れる 私はそう欲張りなアイドル
One day, i will hold everything that i pursue, yes, i am so greedy, true voracious idol
等身大でみんなのことちゃんと愛したいから
So sincerely, what i'm wishing for is to love each of you with all my heart
今日も嘘をつくの この言葉がいつか本当に鳴る日を願って
And so today, I lie again, I'm wishing that one day these words become true
それでもまだ君と君にだけは言えずにいたけど
Up to this day, I've not been able to let you and you hear me saying those meaningful words...
無敵の笑顔で荒らすメディア
With your invincible smile you stir up the media,
知りたいその秘密ミステリアス
I wanna know that secret, it's so mysterious.
抜けてるとこさえ彼女のエリア
Even your flaws are part of your charm,
完璧で嘘つきな君は
You, so perfect and full of lies,
天才的なアイドル様
are a genius idol!
あ、お、聞こえてますか？
Ah... Oh, can you hear me?
こちらステージから離れて、楽屋に来てます！
We've moved away from the stage and are in the dressing room!
ちょっと待ってね
Hey, wait a second!
どうすか？今の気持ち、どうすか？
How is it? How are you feeling right now?
それ先輩、逃げるからちょっと待ってください！
Hey Senpai, I'm gonna run, so hold on a sec!
どうすか？今の気持ち、どうすか？
How is it? How are you feeling right now?
日本語が筋ない？気まぐれの悪い子ですねえ
Can't speak proper Japanese? What a naughty girl.
悪い子は、お叱りだよ。やっちゃってくださいよ！
Naughty kids need to be scolded. Go ahead and do it!
我が送水だぞ！
Behold, our water blaster!
こっちは悪魔と天使のハーフだぞ！
And this here is a half-demon, half-angel!
そんでこっちは番長だぞ！
And this one's the boss!
あー！
Aah!
マスコミ、こんなところに突きなさい！
Press, poke me right here!
さあ、変わって次の楽屋を見てみましょうか
Now then, let's go check out the next dressing room!
こんにちは！わあ、風邪っすよ！
Hello! Whoa, it's so windy!
なんでこの楽屋の風こんな暴風！？
Why is there such a violent storm inside this dressing room?!
風に飛ぶ！飛ぶ！
I'm getting blown away! Flying!
てか何の匂いかすれ？
Wait, what's that smell?
俺たちの出番だな！
It's our turn!
えいっ！
Hah!
楽屋で強風の疑い さくらみこ容疑者を逮捕
[Suspect Sakura Miko arrested for suspected gale in dressing room]
抜け込んでない！やってない！
I didn't sneak in! I didn't do it!
え待って、なんで私まで？
Wait, why am I dragged into this too?!
おお、先輩たちはどうやら捕まってしまいますかねえ
Oh, looks like the seniors ended up getting caught, huh?
僕の楽屋はうわ、臭っさあ！
My dressing room is—ew, so smelly!
気付けのいっぱいじゃ！
Have a drink to wake you up!
ラミーの酒が飲めねえって！
Lamy's sake can't be drunk like this—!
もう飲めねえっす...
I can't drink anymore...
ライブ中なのに出来上がってますねえ
They're completely plastered right in the middle of a live stream.
私はラーメンしゃ！フクロウの出汁が効いてるね！
I am Ramen-sha! Owl dashi makes it taste great!
出汁にしないで！
Don't use me for dashi!
隠し味じゃ足りねえよなあ
Secret ingredients aren't enough, huh?
刺激も足りませんなあ
And we need more kick too.
うん、物足りねえな
Yeah, still not enough.
次げ冥府か！
Next is the underworld!
あ、お客さん、お題がまだだよ
Ah, customer, you still haven't paid!
酒臭くてつまらないね
Smells like booze and it's boring.
手下の部屋に行きましょう！
Let's go to the underling's room!
なんだかおいしそうな匂いがしますね
It smells really delicious.
おいしいね！おいしい！
Delicious! So good!
なんでお前はこんなにおいしいんだ！
Why is it so delicious?!
どんどん焼こう、どんどん！
Keep grilling more and more!
仲間を食べられてますが、
Our comrade is being eaten, but...
今の気持ちはいかがですか？
how are you feeling right now?
わあ、おいしいならそれでよし
Wow, if it's delicious, then all is good.
うっ、からしが入ってる？
Ugh, is there mustard in here?
からしが入ってる？
Mustard is in it?!
こっちは梅干しが！インドネシアが！
Over here has pickled plum! Indonesia is in it!
これビジネスチャンスかも！いろんな味を堪能してね！
This might be a business chance! Enjoy all the different flavors!
タコパーって感じするね
Feels just like a takoyaki party.
じゃあ次の部屋に行きましょう！
Well then, let's head to the next room!
突撃インタビュー！
Surprise interview!
おこちゃん、お？大丈夫かい？
Oko-chan, huh? Are you okay?
突撃インタビューね、お？突撃インタビューね
Surprise interview, huh? Oh? Surprise interview, huh?
ええっと、ええっと、無理にボケなくていいからね
Um, um, you don't have to force yourself to make jokes, okay?
ええ、メルたちの歌、聞いてくれましたか？この後も楽しんでってね
Uh, did you listen to Mel and the others' song? Enjoy the rest of the show!
おいたんしょっく、楽しみだす
Oitan shock, I'm looking forward to it.
ねえなんかおかやも喋ってよ
Hey Okayu, say something too.
にゃんぎ！
Nyangi!
どうですか？
How is it?
え、え、何が？
Eh, eh, what?
いや、なんかインタビューしろって言われて
Well, I was told to do an interview...
どうですか？
How is it?
ちょ、マイク近いから！なんでずるいぞ！何だけ？
Wait, the mic is too close! Why is it unfair? What is it?
どうですか？どう宿ですか？
How is it? How's the inn?
うちは許認可なんだから喋らせるよ！
I'm a licensing authority, so let me talk!
と、いうことでしたー！
That's how it went!
じゃあバトンタッチ！
Then passing the baton.
はーい！次は私たちがインタビューするよ！
Okay! Next, we're going to do the interview!
こんばんは！楽屋突撃インタビューです！
Good evening! It's a dressing room surprise interview!
もうすぐ2023年も終わりますね
2023 is almost coming to an end.
ほんとあっというま！もうすぐ年明け！
Truly in a blink of an eye! The new year is almost here!
インドネシアって時差どれぐらいあるの？インドネシアの年明けは2時間後かな？
How big is the time difference for Indonesia? Indonesia's new year is probably 2 hours later?
2回お祝いできますね！
You can celebrate twice!
お、なんかいいねその考え方
Oh, I like that way of thinking.
カウントダウンまであとどれくらいだろう？
How much longer until the countdown?
あ、やばいもう次行かなきゃ！
Ah, crap, we gotta go to the next one!
それでは次のインタビュアーは狼ミオ先輩！よし、頑張るぞ！
Well then, the next interviewer is Mio Ookami-senpai! Alright, let's do our best!
次はこちらの楽屋！
Next is this dressing room over here.
ほらうるうる、この席は我々ホロのグラフィティが乗っ取らせてもらうぜ！返して！戻してー！俺たちが何したって言うんだ！
Hey, blow by blow, we're taking over this seat! Give it back! Give it back! What did we even do?!
ぐらぐら言うな、年越すぞ！こんなめちゃめちゃ空間で年越したくない！！！
Stop grumbling, we're ringing in the new year! I don't wanna ring in the new year in such a chaotic space!!!
だったら止めてみろ！ブラウザバックするわ！低評価で！草も生えない！
Then try stopping us! I'm browser-backing! With a dislike! Not even funny!
うちの番だけ大荒れ！
Only our turn is a total mess!
なんかトラブルがあったみたいで
It seems like there was some trouble,
ライダー星街彗星！
Rider Hoshimachi Suisei!
こんばんは！すいちゃん！
Good evening! Suichan!
ねずみ小僧の顎が外れた。この顎外れてるってば！
Nezumi-kozou's jaw came unhinged. Her jaw is really unhinged!
とにかくぐってやるしかないかも！
Anyway, we might just have to push it in.
なんでそこで私を見るの？
Why are you looking at me for that?
すいちゃんなら中々なく今週の力でやれるかなって
Figured since it's Suichan, you could do it with your superhuman strength.
声をね！
Watch your voice!
仕方ないなあ。一日の代わりに引き受けて！
Can't be helped. Take it in place of the rat!
じゃあ次の楽屋行きます！
Well then, let's go to the next dressing room!
こんばんは！
Good evening!
あいつは魔法の過剰摂取で沸点がおかしくなったんや。
She overdosed on magic and her boiling point went wonky.
お前も食らええー！
Eat this too!
カボチャ！カボチャ！
Pumpkin! Pumpkin!
何このガキには早いんだよなぁ。
What, this is too early for brats, you know.
お前もガキじゃろがい！ガキって言った方がガキなんですー！
You're a brat too! Saying 'brat' makes you the brat!
危ない！
Careful!
あははは！
Hahaha!
サクサクサクサク…！ちっ…もうつまんない！次のがきへ行こっ！
Crunch, crunch... Tch, boring! Let's go to the next brat!
おじゃま〜！馬鹿騒ぎしてる最中でしょうが！
Pardon the interruption! You guys are in the middle of a crazy party, aren't you?
なんか変なの置き去りになっちゃったのだな。
Looks like some weirdo got left behind.
私たちも混ぜようか、お父さん？
Shall we include us too, dad?
誰が父親だ！
Who's your dad?!
カボチャも寝ろ！カボチャもー！
Pumpkin, go to sleep too! Pumpkin!
しょうがないなぁ、父様が寝かしつけてあげよう。
Can't be helped, Father will put you to sleep.
僕もご一緒していいかな？
May I join you as well?
母さん！あの男は誰だい？
Mother! Who is that man?
違うのよ！違うのよ！
It's not what you think!
あかねちゃんの芝居にも付き合いちまったよ。
I got roped into Akane-chan's play too.
じゃあママがマイクかわるね。
Then Mama will pass the mic.
次のガキやこちらです。
The next brat is over here.
こんばんは〜！
Good evening~!
いやあああ！
Nooooo!
この先輩がまわりすぎて止まりません！止まらない！
This senior is spinning too much and won't stop! She won't stop!
ばわばわばわ……
Bawa bawa bawa...
と、とりあえずインタビューを…マイクが…
F-First, an interview... The mic is...
この状況でインタビューは無理です！ちょこせせも手伝って！ええ〜？
Interviews are impossible in this situation! Chocosec, help out too! Eh~?
じゃあパパと一緒、あやめ様！手伝って、あやめ様〜！
Then together with Papa, Ayame-sama! Help out, Ayame-sama~!
手伝って、あやめ様〜！おっ！
Help out, Ayame-sama~? Oh!
可愛くなくてごめん。いつも暗くて可愛くなくてごめん。
Sorry for not being cute. Always gloomy and not being cute, sorry.
さみしい。可愛くなくてごめん。
Lonely. Sorry for not being cute.
可愛くなくてごめん。宇宙人って、頭脳派がこんなところに！
Sorry for not being cute. An alien mastermind in a place like this!
まだまだこれからステージあるのに、やめてくださいその演出は！
There's still a stage coming up, stop that direction!
あれ？ぺこら先輩は感動ないんでござるか？
Huh? Pekora-senpai, aren't you moved?
かわいくってごめん！このウサギ自己肯定感たかーい！
Sorry for being cute! This rabbit has high self-esteem!
ほらほら、みんな可愛いよ。それでは！
Hey hey, everyone is cute. Now then!
あ、そんなこんなで。あと十数秒で年越しだ！
Ah, and so, just over ten seconds until the new year!
いや、長いようで短かったですね。
Man, it felt long yet short.
来年ももっともっともっと……
Next year, even more, more, more...
みんなと一緒に。
Together with everyone.
ほら、みんな屋上に集まれー！
Hey everyone, gather on the rooftop!
12、11、10、9、8、7、6、5、4、3、2、1…
12, 11, 10, 9, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1...
HAPPY NEW YEAR!!
Everything is gonna be alrightって感じを今 噂のビーウェイン
Everything is gonna be alright, that kind of vibe, wayward rumors right now
Are you ready? コンコンコン Yes 狐にバカされて
Are you ready? Kon-kon-kon, yes, being fooled by a fox
Lock lock lock 心を開いて ウーイエイ
Lock lock lock, open your heart, oo yeah
Everything is gonna be alrightって感じを今 噂のビーウェイン
Everything is gonna be alright, that kind of vibe, wayward rumors right now
Wow wow wow コンコンコン 魔法をかけて 浮気で歩けるまでビーウェイン
Wow wow wow, kon-kon-kon, cast a magic spell, walking flirtatiously until wayward
信じまいに響いてよマイハーリ
Resoundingly echo, my heart
君がいるから私は迷わない
Because you are here, I won't get lost
あぁ、瞬きは恋が傷つき響く
Ah, blinking makes love painful and resounding
つづく道昨日をなぞれ 共になげく夜
The path continues, tracing yesterday, a night lamenting together
遠くへ伝播する想いは心強くする
Feelings propagating far make the heart stronger
ひとりじゃない 隣に君がいるから
I'm not alone, because you're right by my side
確かめ合う道へ…
To the path where we confirm...
信じまいに響いてよマイハーリ
Resoundingly echo, my heart
あぁ、そんなことはない
Ah, that's not true
暗闇にまぎれ 甘いチョコに溶けたい
Want to melt into sweet chocolate in the dark,
いくつも鎖 つなげては解きたい
Connecting multiple chains, yet wanting to untie them,
光の姿 化けた瞳をかして
Lend me your eyes, disguised in the form of light.
純金が痛むのね
Pure gold hurts, doesn't it?
Pin-down, Pin-down 響かせリング・ドン・バラード
Pin-down, pin-down, let the ring-don ballad echo!
Pin-down, Pin-down 流してリング・ドン・ヤミード
Pin-down, pin-down, let the ring-don yamid flow!
闇の先が 闇の先が昂るの
The darkness ahead is surging.
噛みつきやしないわ
I won't bite you.
抱きしめはしないわ
I won't hold you tight.
私のものでね
You are mine.
飽きたらのりすて
When you get bored...
ウサギひょんひょん跳ねて 月まで行けちゃいそうな気分よ
Bunnies hopping around, feeling like I can reach the moon.
白馬に乗った王子様には まだほど遠いけど
Still far from a prince on a white horse,
探し続けた 私だけの太陽
I kept searching for my one and only sun.
見つけたのさ 後ろ指指されたってかまわないほど
I found it, and I don't care if people point fingers.
走り出した鼓動は もう止まらない
This beating heart won't stop anymore!
欲しいのは チョコレート
What I want is chocolate,
甘くてほろ苦い予感
A sweet and bittersweet premonition.
運命の巡り会い ずっと夢に見いていた
Fated encounter, I've always dreamed of this.
恋したら それだけで 誰もがヒロインになれる
When you fall in love, anyone can become a heroine.
一度しかないチャンス ためらわずGETしよう
A once-in-a-lifetime chance, let's grab it without hesitation!
Give me! Love me!
Baby, hold your line
Are you living free?
Let's forget everything and have some fun
Give it to you fast, baby, do you start?
Baby, baby, there's no need to think twice
Give it to you fast
Give it to you, start, baby, do you start?
Evil giving in, 'cause you know you're dressed so high
Cook it up, cut that alarm, oh, you can't kill in a lie
What you doing, bro? Now, are you living free?
One, four, three, two, one, wait, go out!
Care, I'm not playing
Baby, don't care
No, save me, baby
Love, love, love, love, love, crash and burn!
愛のネタバレ 「別れ」ってぽいな
Spoilers of love, looking like a "breakup".
人生のネタバレ 「死ぬ」ってぽいな
Spoilers of life, looking like "death".
なにそれ意味深で それっぽい単語集で
What's with that meaningful, seemingly deep vocabulary?
踊ってんの? 失敬 逆に興奮してきたなあと
Dancing? Excuse me, on the contrary, I'm getting excited!
景気いいけど 品性はthe end Gott ist tot
The economy is good, but decency is the end, Gott ist tot.
神っぽいな それ 卑怯
God-ish, that's unfair.
神っぽいな それ my god
God-ish, that's my god.
IQが下がっていく感じ
Feeling my IQ dropping.
邪心っぽいな それ 畢竟
Wicked-hearted, after all.
邪心っぽいな それ my god
Wicked-hearted, that's my god.
害虫はどっちだ
Which one of us is the pest?
その髪型 その目 その口元
That hairstyle, those eyes, those lips.
その香水 その服 アレっぽいな
That perfume, those clothes, that's like—
その名言 その意見 その批評
That famous quote, that opinion, that critique.
神っぽいな それ 卑怯
God-ish, that's unfair.
神っぽいな メタ思考する本質は悪意
God-ish, meta-thinking essence is malice.
人を小馬鹿にしたような作為 無為に生き延びるのは難しい
Artifice that looks down on people, hard to survive aimlessly.
権力に飲まれて揺らぐ灯り 神を否定し神に成り代わり
Lights swaying swallowed by power, denying God and replacing Him.
玉座で豹変する小物の達 批判に見せかけ自己の祈り
Petty creatures changing on the throne, disguised critique as self-prayer.
Do you know 何言ってんの 何言ってんの それ
Do you know what you're saying, what you're saying?
意味がよくわかんないし 眠っちまうよ マジ
I don't really get the meaning, I'm falling asleep, seriously!
飽きっぽいんだよ オーケー 飽きっぽいんだよ オーケー
Getting bored, okay? Getting bored, okay?
さあ、ざざたたたた、まるで黙ったままでいよう
Now, let's stay silent as if...
言えないね、そんな強い言葉は少しだけ静かにしてほしいね
I can't say such strong words, I want you to be a little quiet.
ああ 私たちだいぶ、今更みたいに思いたかったはずなのに
Ah, we should have wanted to think it's way past that now.
世界ぜんぜん征服や 闇見やるその日までね
Conquering the world, until the day we look at the darkness.
どんどん征服や 今宵のことだよよよ待って
Keep conquering, it's tonight, wait!
先生ぜんぜん征服や あなたの街で完全体で作るわ
Creating a complete body in your town!
魅惑を隠す箱 秘宝に匂う危なげな Danger Marine Smell ❤️Ahoy❤️
A box hiding allure, a dangerous marine smell scenting the treasure.
誘うガーネットの赤 極上の海賊の秘宝 それは私 艶が溢れ漏れる香りをどうか怯えないで
The red of inviting garnet, the ultimate pirate's treasure, that is me.
開けてみて Sexy世界一 Superピチピチ ぶっちょけ船長捕まえたくなーい?
Try opening it, world's sexiest, super fresh! Don't you want to catch Captain Houshou?
月影が消えてゆく
Moonlight fading away...
指先がゆらゆらと
Fingertips are swaying gently.
その動きが止まった時計の針に踏み込んだ
That movement stopped time when I stepped into the clock's realm.
雲が咲いた 誰じゃ？
Could it be that the clouds are blooming?
其の黒髪 その笑顔を
So you know that starry hair and that smile!
牙を出し叫べ ずっきゅんだ
Showing my fangs and screaming, it's all or nothing.
あたしは噛み付いたら離さないにゃ
I won't let go once I bite down.
剥がれ落ちたメイク すっぴんのアニマル 醜くてもやっちゃうのよ
An ugly animal that's still doing it anyway.
もっとしたい もっとしたい もっと頂戴
I want more, I want more, I want it now!
雲っちゃいたいなら 唇尖らせて ポップコーンぷち
Can't get enough, can't wait, making my throat go hoarse until I drop!
ポップコーンぷち
Until I drop!
I'm a swinging cat, Kick Snare Hihat, Groovy growl ほら騒々しい音が鳴るよ
I'm a swinging cat, kick, snare, hi-hat, groovy growl, hey, noisy sounds ring out.
I got to be free, Take it easy 今日もぐんぐん育う心身
I got to be free, take it easy, growing my mind and body today too!
食べる寝る遊ぶ繰り返しピンピン You know?
Eating, sleeping, playing on repeat, pin-pin, you know?
気軽にやってくるピンチ だから用意する本気スイッチ
Easy pinches come easily, so I get my serious switch ready.
だってこの世はヘルキッチン You know?
You know this world is a hell kitchen?
両方の目で獲物を見定めている 心の奥すぐる香り 満ちた月のように丸めてる モノクロに咲く鮮やかなハーモニー
Staring at my prey with both eyes, a vibrant harmony blooming in monochrome.
Grrr Grrr Tummy, Ready steady go!
Mogu Mogu Yummy, Meow Meow Kitty
ぼくが君の神様になったげる お願い!お願い!しょうがないなあー
I'll become your god, so please, please, you have to!
お願い!お願い!たすけておかうにゃん!
Please, please, save me, Okayu!
やぁやぁ、悩める人類の皆様 けったいな時代の只中 自分の事さえ、愛せない
Hey, hey, troubled humans everywhere, in this harsh age, you can't even love yourselves.
「誰かに認めてもらいたいな...」 「何も上手くいかずヤダヤダ」
"I want someone to acknowledge me," "Nothing goes right, I hate it, I hate it."
神頼みそれなのに どこに行ったら会えるの神様
Relying on gods, when you wonder where to find one...
(Help me!) どうしたの~? (Help me!) うんうん
Help me! What's wrong? Help me! Yeah, yeah.
(Help me!) そっか~大変だね~ (Save me!) でもね~ (Save me!) 大丈夫!
Help me! Wow, that's a big deal! Save me! But you know, save me! It's alright!
ぼくが味方でいるからさ~ 生きているだけで満点
Because I'm on your side! Just living is a perfect score!
自信持ちなさい全部 信じていいいい当然 君はとっても素敵だよ!
You can have confidence, absolutely! You can believe it, of course!
ありとあらゆる この世の全てを
All praise to everything in this world!
Parade, parade, parade! 輝くんだよ 呼び合う声を 合図に
Parade, parade, parade! Let's shine brightly, using our calling voices as a signal.
Parade, parade, parade! 探しに行くよ スタートは 何回だって
Parade, parade, parade! Let's go search, how many times is this our start?
Parade, parade, parade! 輝くんだよ 悔しさも 愛しさも 連れておいでて
Parade, parade, parade! Let's shine brightly! Bring along your regrets and your love.
風、夢、羽 飛び立てるさ
Wind, dream, feather, let's make them take flight!
Parade, parade, parade! 輝くんだよ 暗がりを満たすのは 君だ、 ボクだ
Parade, parade, parade! Let's shine brightly! Filling up the darkness, you are the one who is the star.
Parade, parade, parade! 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade! Let's shine brightly!
悔しさもいとおしさも すべてを おいてゆこう 健康で
Let's put all those cute little things by our side and go through all weathers!
ささやかな願いは光
Don't whisper, let's have a bright smile!
終わりなき兆し 君を見つけたこと 胸を張れるよ
The endless signs, finding you makes me so proud!
Parade, parade, parade! 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade! Let's shine brightly!
はぴー新年 そろそろ考えなくちゃ
Happy New Year, I need to start thinking soon.
みんながちょっとうるさいし まずは作戦会議
Everyone's being noisy, so first, a strategy meeting.
おっけー元旦 今から始まる
Okay, New Year's Day, starting now,
ラブストーリーとか そんなんじゃないし
It's not like some love story or anything.
本命なんだし 今日が本番なんてうそうそ
He's my true love, saying today's the main event is no way!
大事なのはここから一ヶ月でジレったいな
The important part is the agonizing month starting from here.
大人になったってドキドキしてたいもんだって
Even as adults, we want our hearts to race, right?
両思いの先走り うんと
Jumping the gun on mutual feelings, yeah...
甘い甘い甘い甘いの好き好き好き好き
So sweet, sweet, sweet, sweet, love, love, love, love!
っていう私が選んだ君はとびきりのスウィート
You, chosen by me, are the ultimate sweet!
甘い甘い甘い甘い1年で
Sweet, sweet, sweet, sweet, in a whole year,
一番の贅沢でもしちゃいましょうよ
let's indulge in the greatest luxury!
ちょっちょちょっとチョコレートは
Just a, just a, just a bit of chocolate,
予算とかカロリーとかはオーバーでもね ああ
even if it goes over budget and calories, oh!
ちょっちょちょっとチョコレート、
Just a, just a, just a bit of chocolate,
私の恋とかにごほうびをあげたい
I want to give a reward to my love.
もう今日だってだいたいは決めました
I've pretty much decided as of today.
おうち用ですかってなんでわかったの
"Is this for home use?" How did you know?!
そうでもやっぱみんなソワソワしちゃうねそりゃそうだけどね
Even so, everyone gets restless, well of course they do.
余裕見せたらそれも変化なねえ呼び出しなんてなになに
If I act composed, will that change things? Hey, what's this sudden call?
今日のところは帰って楽しみタイノにナ
I wanted to go home and enjoy today, but...
でもあれ私がほしかったかわいいやつじゃない ?
But wait, isn't that the cute thing I wanted?
気になるこれって片思いのまれて
I'm curious, is this unrequited love?
甘い甘い甘い甘いの好き好き好き好き
So sweet, sweet, sweet, sweet, love, love, love, love!
そんな私にあなたがくれたとびきりのサプライズ
A surprise like no other that you gave to someone like me!
やばいやばいやばいやばいそんなこと
No way, no way, no way, no way, I never imagined such a thing,
想像もしなかったの眠れないね一ヶ月も悩むなんて
I won't be able to sleep, agonizing for a whole month!
そんなの無理じゃない
Isn't that impossible?
一ヶ月も悩むなんてそんなの無理じゃない
Agonizing for a whole month isn't possible!
私毎日が本命全力そういうのが好きでごめん
My every day is all-out true love, sorry if you like that kind of thing.
うんとうんとうんとうんとうんとすきすきすきすき
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, love, love, love, love!
っていう私が選んだ君はとびきりのスウィート
You, chosen by me, are the ultimate sweet!
甘い甘い甘い甘い1年で
Sweet, sweet, sweet, sweet, in a whole year,
一番の贅沢でもしちゃいましょうよ
let's indulge in the greatest luxury!
ちょっちょちょっとチョコレートは
Just a, just a, just a bit of chocolate,
予算とかカロリーとかはオーバーでもね ああ
even if it goes over budget and calories, oh!
ちょっちょちょっとチョコレート、
Just a, just a, just a bit of chocolate,
私の恋とかにごほうびをあげたい
I want to give a reward to my love.
ちょっちょちょっとチョコレートは
Just a, just a, just a bit of chocolate,
予算とかカロリーとかはオーバーでもね ああ
even if it goes over budget and calories, oh!
ちょっちょちょっとチョコレート、
Just a, just a, just a bit of chocolate,
私の恋とかにごほうびをあげたい
I want to give a reward to my love.
私の今日からごほうびをあげたい
I want to give a reward starting from my today.
もっとすり抜けていくシャンデリア
Slipping right through the chandelier...
1・2・3 落としてくシャンデリア
1, 2, 3, falling chandeliers,
一斉に火を灯すネオンライト
neon lights igniting all at once.
4・5・6 鳴らせクラップ
4, 5, 6, make the applause ring,
スポットライト浴びて
bathed in spotlights.
さあ、ようこそテアトルへ
Now, welcome to the theater!
開催さ イッツ・ショウ・タイム
The curtain rises, it's show time!
ショウタイム・ルーラー
[Song: Showtime Ruler]
ちらっと踊るステップ踏んだ
Stepping with a quick dance step,
誘導視線は向こうのハート
guiding your gaze to the heart over there.
急転直下
A sudden nosedive,
心臓はチック＆トーク ほらQ&Aアクション
heart goes tick-tock, hey, Q&A action!
7・8 上がっていく
7, 8, rising up,
9・10 揺ないでいく
9, 10, swaying on.
緊張感を解き放つ
Releasing the tension,
この一瞬へご招待
inviting you to this very moment.
アンプ・アップ 僕の感性をアンプ・アップ 更新中
Amp up, my sensitivity, amp up, updating,
アンプ・アップ 君の感性をアンプ・アップ 挑戦中
amp up, your sensitivity, amp up, challenging.
アンプ・アップ 研ぎ澄ませていく アンプ・アップ この一瞬
Amp up, sharpening it, amp up, this moment,
アンプ・アップ 君の感情の支配者さ
amp up, the ruler of your emotions!
イッツ・ショウ・タイム
It's show time!
テイク・ユー・ハイアー
Take you higher!
もっとクレイジーに クレイジーにしちゃって
Get more crazy, let's get crazy!
イッツ・ショウ・タイム
It's show time!
テイク・ユー・ハイアー
Take you higher!
もっと自由に 夢中にご招待
Inviting you to be freer and lost in a dream.
夢みたいな時間 さあ、もっと声を聴かせてちょうだいな
A dreamlike time, now, let me hear your voices more!
湧き上がる感情の狂気が君を呑み込んでさ
The madness of surging emotions swallows you up,
ぼくを呑み込んでさ
swallows me up.
生も負も悲も歓もぼくの思い通り
Life, defeat, sorrow, and joy are all just as I desire.
二度と孤独になんてなれないよぼくの合図で
You can never be lonely again, on my cue.
Don't take your eyes away
イッツ・ショウ・タイム
it's show time,
That's right!
この時ボクらはひとつになっていく
At this time, we become one,
会場に響くこの歓声
echoing this cheer throughout the venue.
毎秒描き出す世界で 壇上から揺さぶる感性
In the world painted every second, our sensibilities shake from the stage.
泣きそうになるほどに重なる
Overlapping to the point of tears.
気のおけない under the control
Carefree under the control,
今僕らの思いは連動 君の鼓動そいつがショウタイム
now our feelings are linked, your heartbeat—that's showtime!
そう僕らを繋ぐよ ショウタイム テイク・ユー・ハイアー
Yes, connecting us, showtime, take you higher!
もっとクレイジーに クレイジーにしちゃって
Get more crazy, let's get crazy,
ショウタイム テイク・ユー・ハイアー
showtime, take you higher!
もっと自由に 夢中にご招待 夢みたいな時間
Inviting you to be freer and lost in a dream, a dreamlike time.
さあもっと声を聴かせてちょうだいな
Now, let me hear your voices more!
湧き上がる感情の狂乱が
The frenzy of surging emotions
君を呑み込んでさ ぼくを呑み込んでさ
swallows you up, swallows me up.
生も負も悲も歓もぼくの思い通り
Life, defeat, sorrow, and joy are all just as I desire.
二度と孤独になんてなれないよぼくの合図で
You can never be lonely again, on my cue.
Don't take your eyes away
イッツ・ショウ・タイム
it's show time,
That's right!
この時ボクらはひとつになっていく 会場に響くこの歓声
At this time, we become one, echoing this cheer throughout the venue.
夢みたいな時間 さあ、もっと声を聴かせてちょうだいな
A dreamlike time, now, let me hear your voices more!
湧き上がる感情の狂気が君を呑み込んでさ ぼくを呑み込んでさ
The madness of surging emotions swallows you up, swallows me up.
生も負も悲も歓もぼくの思い通り
Life, defeat, sorrow, and joy are all just as I desire.
踊れ 踊れ 熱くなるため 人は生まれたはずさ
Dance, dance, people were born to get passionate!
いま小さく燃えてる まだ小さな燠が
Now burning small, a still-small ember,
ひとつになれば奇跡が生まれ この世界はいつもあきらめない心に
if they become one, a miracle is born; this world always rewards an unflinching heart.
MY舞☆TONIGHT
[Song: MY舞☆TONIGHT]
答えじゃなく 道を探す 手掛かりをくれるから
Not giving answers, but clues to find the way,
最後まで気強で行こう
so let's press on bravely to the very end!
踊れ 踊れ 熱くなるため 人は生まれてきたの?
Dance, dance, were people born to get passionate?
踊れ 踊れ きっとそうだよ だから夢見て踊ろう
Dance, dance, surely it's so, so let's dream and dance!
MY舞TONIGHT 最高の日々にしよう!
MY舞 TONIGHT, let's make it the best days!
強気でいこう
Let's go in strong!
踊れ 踊れ
Dance, dance!
熱くなるため 人は生まれてきたの
People were born to grow passionate!
踊れ 踊れ きっと空よ
Dance, dance, surely the sky—
だから 夢見て踊ろう
So let's dream and dance!
MY MY TONIGHT
My, My, Tonight—
最高潮の
at our peak!
MY MY TONIGHT
My, My, Tonight—
距離にしよう
let's close the distance!
いつか広がるだろう ほら大きく広がれ
Someday it will spread out, look, spread wide!
頑張る力 奇跡を呼んでる
The power of hard work calls forth miracles!
この世界の中で 輝きたい心があつまる時
In this world, when hearts wanting to shine gather—
新しいこと 思いつき走りダス
a new idea strikes and we start running!
足元が見えないけど
Even though our footing is out of sight,
羽根みたいに 手伸ばして
like wings, we reach out our hands!
踊れ 踊れ 憧れたのは
Dance, dance, what we longed for
ずっと 瞬く光
is a light that twinkles forever!
踊れ 踊れ きっといつかは
Dance, dance, surely one day
叶うはずだと踊ろう
it will come true, so let's dance!
MY MY TONIGHT
My, My, Tonight—
明日へと
toward tomorrow!
MY MY TONIGHT
My, My, Tonight—
つなげよう
let's connect!
迷いの声に 導かれて
Guided by the voice of hesitation,
道がまた 開けたよ
the path has opened up once more!
最後まで 強気でいこう
Let's stay strong right to the end!
踊れ 踊れ
Dance, dance!
熱くなるため 人は生まれてきたの
People were born to grow passionate!
踊れ 踊れ きっとそうだよ
Dance, dance, that's definitely right!
だから 夢見て踊ろう
So let's dream and dance!
MY MY TONIGHT
My, My, Tonight—
最高潮の
at our peak!
MY MY TONIGHT
My, My, Tonight—
距離にしよう
let's close the distance!
MY MY TONIGHT ダンシングナイト
My, My, Tonight, Dancing Night!
せーの！ ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Ready, set! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
おにぎりこんばんわん
Onigiri, good evening!
ライブ最高でした！
The live was amazing!
感想をホロプラスに投稿っと。
Posting my thoughts to Holoplus...
あけましておめでとうございます！ ホロプラス宣伝隊長の春先のどかです！
Happy New Year! I'm Harusaki Nodoka, Holoplus PR Captain!
公式アプリ「ホロプラス」ではカウントダウンライブ連動キャンペーンを開催中です！
The official app "Holoplus" is holding a countdown live collaboration campaign!
推し活するだけでプレゼントが当たるチャンス…！？
A chance to win prizes just by supporting your oshi...!?
詳しくは「ホロプラス」をチェック！
Check "Holoplus" for details!
2024年も「ホロプラス」をよろしくお願いいたします！
Please continue to support "Holoplus" in 2024 as well!
おつホロプラス～！
Otsu Holoplus~!
聞いて きれいじゃない きれいじゃないでも 嫌いじゃない嫌いじゃないでしょ
Listen... It's not pretty, it's not pretty, but don't you hate it?
まっすぐに不器用でもいい
Even being straight and clumsy is fine.
どうでもいい どうでもいいんだよ 君を襲うどんな雨も
It doesn't matter at all, whatever rain attacks you,
水たまり踏みつけて 笑われたっていいんだよ
stomp on the puddles, it's okay to be laughed at.
溢れたっていいんだから 恐れずに前を向いたら息をして見て
Because it's okay to overflow. Look ahead without fear and take a breath.
コンコンキツネ！
Kon-kon kitsune!
ふわふわしっぽのごんぼせい、あなたの心の一番星、白上フブキです！
The fluffy-tailed, number one star in your heart, I'm Shirakami Fubuki!
ハイ、フレンズ！
Hi, friends!
皆さん、速報じゃい！
Everyone, breaking news!
来る2024年1月5日に、そう、パトラちゃんと3Dコラボ配信が決定しました！イエーイ！
Coming January 5th, 2024, that's right—a 3D collab stream with Patra-chan has been decided! Yay!
1月5日は白上チャンネルで行いますので皆さん、お楽しみに！
January 5th will be on Shirakami's channel, so everyone, look forward to it!
では最後にパトラちゃんから一言！
Now, lastly, a word from Patra-chan!
こんばんわわ！周防パトラです。
Good evening-wawa! I'm Suou Patra.
1月5日、ホロライブスタジオに遊びに行っちゃうよん！
On January 5th, I'm going to visit the Hololive studio!
皆さん、よろしくお願いします！
Everyone, please treat me well!